Speaker 1: Motorola Edge 40 Pro
Speaker 1: tipped to cost more
Speaker 1: than edge 30 pro key
Speaker 1: specifications leaked
Speaker 1: Motorola Edge 40
Speaker 1: series including a base
Speaker 1: and a pro variant was
Speaker 1: expected to be
Speaker 1: launched at the mobile
Speaker 1: World Congress event
Speaker 1: earlier this year.
Speaker 1: However, the series
Speaker 1: announcement was a
Speaker 1: no show at the
Speaker 1: Barcelona conference
Speaker 1: and the company is yet
Speaker 1: to officially confirm a
Speaker 1: launch date
Speaker 1: for the phones.
Speaker 1: Despite no information
Speaker 1: from the Lenovo
Speaker 1: owned brand, there
Speaker 1: have been multiple
Speaker 1: leaks and rumors
Speaker 1: surrounding the
Speaker 1: purported Motorola Ed
Speaker 1: 40 and Motorola Edge
Speaker 1: 40 prom smartphones.
Speaker 1: A new report has now
Speaker 1: leaked the complete
Speaker 1: specifications of the
Speaker 1: rumored devices and a
Speaker 1: tipster has hinted at
Speaker 1: the price of the
Speaker 1: Motorola H 40 Pro
Speaker 1: check the description
Speaker 1: for more details.
Speaker 1: